https://www.lawcrossing.com/lcprivacy.php

Join LawCrossing today
Employers, Post jobs now!
PRIVACY
LawCrossing will NEVER sell or share ANY of your personal information with ANY third party, ever.
All information that our customers provide is held in the utmost care and security and will NEVER be shared with ANY third party.
SECURITY
The LawCrossing servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator (versions 2.0 and higher), Mozilla, Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 3.0 and higher), and AOL (AOL 3.0 and higher). This encryption provides the best possible protection from unauthorized parties accessing any information you send to us.
Why is your privacy so important to us?
LawCrossing is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and we are firmly devoted to maintaining your trust in us. We work extremely hard at safeguarding our customers' important information and keeping it secure. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand our genuine dedication to preserving your privacy.
Confidentiality and discretion are the cornerstones of every job search. We consistently challenge ourselves to rise above every competitor in our honesty and discretion, and we believe we have met this challenge day after day.
What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?
In order to register as a LawCrossing member, users are required to provide pertinent contact information such as their name, an email address, and a mailing address. To complete the sign-up process and subscribe to the service, users are also required to provide financial information, in the form of a valid credit card number and billing address. After subscribing, members may also provide personally identifiable information for other purposes in their use of the site. This includes, but is not limited to, submitting a resume or cover letter. However, any submitted resume or cover letter is viewable only by the person who uploaded or pasted it into the account. Any transmission of these materials can only be achieved through the initiative of the user. LawCrossing does not collect personal information from its subscribers unless they voluntarily and knowingly provide it to us. This means that a user can visit our site without telling us who they are and without revealing any personally identifiable information. The site visitor is never required to provide any personally identifiable information, unless he or she would like to subscribe to the service.
Tell a Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, you are asked to provide a friend's name and email address. LawCrossing will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. LawCrossing does not store this information.
How is the information used?
When you supply personal information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the service or information you have requested). Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary in order to respond to your inquiries regarding the service. Every communication with LawCrossing is held in strictest confidence and handled with integrity. None of your personal information will be disclosed to a potential employer without you taking affirmative action to disclose this information. Your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties under any circumstances, except as disclosed in this privacy statement. Any general demographic information that we receive will never be utilized to identify you. While it may be used for research purposes in order to further develop our understanding of the job market or to improve the Web site, none of this demographic information is attributable to your account. This general information may be disseminated or published in its basic form.
LawCrossing will never sell, share, rent, or trade any personal information about any of our customers to any third parties for their promotional use or other purposes. We will never sell, share, rent, or trade your email address or any other contact information to any third parties for promotional purposes or any other purposes.
LawCrossing will not share any information relating to your employment situation with any third parties, except when required by law. Furthermore, we will not share any information from your resume with any third parties, except when required by law. Any such information which you provide to us will remain completely confidential. Each employee of LawCrossing signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement to ensure your privacy.
LawCrossing is a dba of Employment Crossing, one of the Juriscape companies, which include Attorney Research Group, BCG Attorney Search, CLE Authority, EdFed, Employment Crossing, General Counsel Consulting, Hound.com, JD Journal, JD2B, Judged, Law Firm Staff, Professional Authority, Resume Apple, and Southlake Properties LLC. Each company is a distinct and separately incorporated entity, and each company's databases and servers are maintained independently. The fact that you contacted LawCrossing will never be shared with any other Juriscape company or its employees. Each employee of each company signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement, ensuring that they do not disclose your private information to any other person or company.
After contacting LawCrossing, you may be notified of the potentially complementary services of another Juriscape company. However, no information regarding your employment status, or information from your resume, will ever be shared with any other Juriscape company. Furthermore, the fact that the offer is coming from another Juriscape company will be fully disclosed in the mailing, and you may opt out of such offers at any time as described below. No information will be used for purposes of such offers except your name, contact address, and year of graduation if applicable, and access to such information will be restricted to the sole purpose of communicating with you. Moreover, all other personal information, such as employment status or information from your resume, will not be shared with any other Juriscape company, unless required by law.
Material Changes
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.
If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Security
Personally identifiable information is stored on our database and is not publicly accessible. All LawCrossing employees must sign non-disclosure contracts that ensure the confidentiality of all personally identifiable information before gaining access to such information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, and meets or exceeds all industry standards for the protection and confidentiality of personally identifiable information. The site uses 128 bit SSL encryption to safeguard all financial information.
Opt-out
If you have registered to receive our newsletter, job updates and/or any other automatically distributed information, you may change this registration status at any time. Simply contact us to have your name removed from the particular distribution list you wish to be removed from. This can be achieved in several ways:
Click the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of any automatic email update or alert that you receive:
http://www.lawcrossing.com/lcunsubscribe.php
Send an email to: opt-out@lawcrossing.com
Send correspondence to the following address:
Consumer Privacy DepartmentLawCrossing286 West 100 North,Ephraim, UT, 84627 USA
Furthermore, you may opt-out of receiving emails from other Juriscape companies at any time by clicking on the appropriate "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any such email.
Correct/Update
If you would like to edit your personal information, password, or other settings, simply log in to your account and click on the "My Account" link towards the top of the page. You can also contact us using any method listed at http://www.lawcrossing.com/lchelp.php.
To change your credit card information, please call one of our customer service representatives at (800) 973-1177. If your credit card has been lost or has not been granted approval by Verisign, when you attempt to log-in, you will be prompted to sign-up for an account. Simply enter the prior account information along with your new credit card information. All inquiries will receive responses within 30 days of our receipt of them.
If you want to delete your profile, please contact one of our customer service representatives at (800) 973-1177.
What anonymous information is collected on this site?
IP addresses are briefly logged but discarded within a short period of time. No anonymous information that may be received from visitors is used in any of our work, promotions, or research. These logged files are not connected to a subscriber's personally identifiable information.
How does this site use cookies?
LawCrossing uses cookies to identify your browser as you visit pages on the LawCrossing site. The cookies are used to present dynamic content so that you are not presented with identical content on every visit. No information from the cookies is used in any of our work, promotions or research. None of the cookies used by LawCrossing are connected to your personal information.
We use a third-party tracking service (LinkShare) that uses cookies (log files) to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate (usage, volume statistics and referrals) to monitor the traffic flow and provide targeted service referrals.
Links to external pages
This site may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site. LawCrossing is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites.
Legal Disclaimer
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LawCrossing.
We Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties in the following ways:
Agents
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
Service Providers
We use a third party, VeriSign, to provide Credit Card Processing for our Web site. When you sign up for LawCrossing membership, we share your name, username and billing address to process a charge on your credit card. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.
Testimonials and Live Help
Live Chat help is provided in real-time format on LawCrossing. The user is not required to provide any identifying information in order to make use of the Live Chat function. Any information, such as a name or Username, that is shown to the Customer Service Representative conducting the Live Chat is provided voluntarily by the user and is discarded when the Chat session expires. Any information that is received in the Live Chat sessions is utilized only for the purpose the user intends it to be used for, and is not saved unless the user requests an action of the Customer Service Representative that requires it be saved.
Any testimonials that are provided through the site are published only with a customer's first name and last initial. Testimonials can also be published anonymously, or with only the person's legal field or practice area listed. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial
For more information
If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this statement, please email
privacy@lawcrossing.com.
Let's Do It!
Email:
Get Access
Only LawCrossing consolidates every job it can find in the legal industry and puts all of the job listings it locates in one place.
We have more than 25 times as many legal jobs as any other job board.
We list jobs you will not find elsewhere that are hidden in small regional publications and employer websites.
We collect jobs from more than 250,000 websites and post them on our site.
Increase your chances of being seen! Employers on public job boards get flooded with applications.
Our private job boards ensure that only members can apply to our job postings.
Read more...
Success Stories
I came back to LawCrossing to search through the listings in my new job search because I had been able to get my last 2 jobs through using the site. I love the search capacity and filters. This is a very valuable service.
Jennifer Guidea Bloomfield, NJ
Share Your Success Stories
+ Read More Success Stories
Why You'll Love LawCrossing
Click here
Legal Job Market Updates
Stay Ahead. Get your weekly career digest giving you:
the latest legal jobs
legal employment news and trends
career advice and more
Get Access
Questions?
What is LawCrossing?
Who Else Is Ready to Never Have to Worry About Recessions and the Legal Job Market Again?
Why Job Boards Are Evil!
Blow Away Your Competition with LawCrossing
Get More Employers to Respond to Your Applications and Hire You
Who Else Wants Their Phone Ringing Off the Hook With Quality Job Interviews?
Shoot for the moon. Even if you miss it, you will land among the stars.
